[music]
[музыка]
engri type of delivery,
энгри вид поставки
what else are you and it’s okay okay
чем иначе ты и выдно нормально нормально
you’re okay okay we’ve climbed
че ты нормально выдно мы знов забралась
into the matches of the comandante beams again, which means
на матчи команданте балочки а значит ещё
we’ll still be and today we’ll strengthen the field of cotton wool, and
мы будем а сегодня пит полю ваты вот и
we’ll be richer informative
укрепила будем богаче информативном я
I started out
начинал
I decided to smoke better on the skin streamers
решил покурить better на кожном устреми
guess the edges and keddah puma puma
догадываетесь краины и keddah puma puma
at night you are like that but
ночью ты так и но
still she is a little
все таки она чуть
Svetlana chicksey smaller also a plan for
светлане chicksey меньшим тоже план на
someone
чью-то
kind and
добрый и
on the skin stream we will guess and
на кожному стриме мы будем отгадывать и
let it be like rubber like yes we help the edge
пусть как резину яко да помогаем край
so that is  on each stream we will
так то есть на каждом стриме мы будем
remember some country that
вспоминать какую-то страну которая
helps ukraine which is a friendly
помогает украина которые дружественную
glue and today our ukraine and another is
клей и сегодняшнюю нашу украину и другом
not lithuania so today in our stream we
не литва так сегодня в нашем стриме мы
will remember a country that is
будем вспоминать о такой стране которая
friendly for ukraine like 2
дружественное есть для украины как ли 2
so i bach that is us myself  good evening
так я бачу то есть нам сам добрый вечер
everyone slide you are loretta avramenko you just
всем slide вы лоретта авраменко вы прям
got to the right place max love write
попали туда куда нужно макс любим пишем
iklit them where you can go to
айклит им куда смоленскому можно сходить
smolensk and the train and so the people of shiva  I wasn’t distracted,
и поезд и так народ шиве я не отвлекался
write to him to teach him, yes, you can train a
напишите ему учить ему да можно поездах
little one, and we’ll
маленькому а мы
fix it as far as we directly taught this dish, the
починим докуда за прямо учил это блюдо
reception is on and let’s say that their dates in
прием на и скажем этот их финики в
Russian Tatyana of them
российских татьян из них
go to the Olympics so nothing we are about and
ехать на олимпиаду так ничего мы про и
pacino they start our today’s stream
пачино им начинаем наш сегодняшний стрим
in distant information about  lithuania so and himself
в далекой информации про литву так а сам
from the heading without google and
из рубрики без гугла и
it’s where the axis is.
она куда ось т.к.
a count or two failures of your strength to climb
кол или два провала сила свою на залазь
on to ask rick and who is twisting it is almost a
на просить рик а кто крутишь она почти
date so a rubric without google when lithuania
дату так рубрика без гугла когда литва
proclaimed its independence from the ussr
провозгласила свою независимость от ссср
write a year and who is cooler write the
напишите год а кто круче напишите прям
exact exact date
точную дату давайте
who can be counted and
называешь есть кто в можно посчитать и
kirik oshey date
кирик ошэй дату
passed the exam to the beginning of the porsche vlogs
сдала экзамен к началу влогов porsche
he was tortured so that this is not the food of svetikov
его пытали даб это не еда светикова
azars the rich have a view of the porch very
азаров у богатых вид крыльца очень
much for food then a rubric without google cool
так на пищи то рубрика без гугла cool
or two having voted in june i laid
или два проголосовав в июне я заложил
it down when lithuania declared its
когда литва провозгласила свою
independence from the ussr of the
независимость от ссср
rich  then it flares 90 wider because we are
богатых то пышет 90 пошире потому что мы
still flying over the Rogin union collapsed in
пролетаем еще рогинский союз распался в
90 porsche to him so ukraine having voted
90 porsche ему так украина проголосовав
90 hello yes you will do this doubly someone thread
90 алло да вы буду это вдвойне кто-нить
no matter how two for the operation from
как бы то ни было два на операцию из
all the republics the failure of the
всех республик провалу шила
vyhi trojan union so and
выхи троянскую союзу так и
correctly the view will appear
правильно вид появится
11 March
11 березня
1990 lesson
1990 уроку
, rocky before the
, рокки до
collapse of the radian whom they pop like at a time
развала радианс кого суют как и за раз
we
мы
at a time we succumb to daiki moments and
за раз мы поддаёмся daiki моменты и
qibla so ka
киблы так как
today we have someone who listens to us in Russian
сегодня у нас кто нас слушает по-русски
today we have
сегодня у нас
a friendly wedge on the stream, or
на стриме дружественно нам клина либо
so we have a
так мы
new guess about Georgia axes, not
новый разгадывала про грузию топоров не
so in 2 voted for power in the
так вот в 2 проголосовано за власть в
ninetieth mouth, so I am the x-axis on the article, I
девяностом ротик так я ось х на статья я
adjust the pictures and the movie is  mine clock is
регулирую фотки да и кино это шахте часы
cool and we have a
cool и у нас
great initiative of the scarlet dug so-and-so to do
великий почин алых вырыты так-то to do
as you is he then all the all-ins plucked up
as you is he то вся олл-ины набралась
courage lithuania lithuania was in the forefront of
смелости литва литва была в авангарде
co2 and
co2 и
domineering in the eleventh at dan to
властная в одиннадцатом у дэна чтобы
size 2000
размер 2000
1990 lithuania voted for
1990 го року литва проголосовано за
personality nogai stay  us souls are
личность ногайский stay us души
economical and I think the rich are those who are
экономично и я думаю богатов то кто
older rumpled padike
постарше помятая падике
was called children battle for the otello center
называлась дети битва за отелло центр
so here in vilnius tse buv
так тут вильнюсе це був
.  .  such 90 pass than 90 scab
. . такие 90 пасе чем 90 паршина
appear
появляюсь
sich in infection pleases
sich in зараза радует
blue windows all shot 90 wide
синий виндовсе снятого 90 по широкому
vegan union to the right into tanks to wine
веганский союз направо в танки на винную
people went out there defended
люди вышли там защищал
their places
свои места
[music]
[музыка]
people you replace this alla power lithuania
людей тебе замену это алла власти литва
insults stood your name
обид стояла свою называешь
what tanks
то что танки
13 90 fallen  hand in
13 90 падшего руку
vilnius was the barricades the one who
вильнюсе находилась баррикады тот кто в
twice before entering the disintegration of the very already
раза до ввода распаду самого уже
final points of the disintegration of the vegan union
финальные точки распаду веганскую союзу
fought for his own on the spool on and parshev
боролась за свою на золотник на и паршев
was a stream he mischief
было ручьем он им на это mischief
terabytes for them and answer the
терабайт и отвечай на
puppy on the site sracha on the barricades that's the
щенка на сайте срачи на баррикады вот то
same thing you could bachata  on the Maidan and who
самое вы могли бачаты на майдане а кто
cried and people who I
плакал и люди кто я
turned out to be true aim the carabashnik of
получался в истину цельтесь карабаш ник
leaving
ухода
top-top in the ninety-first lesson
топ-топ в девяносто первом уроке
9190 murat strength two failures strength
9190 мурат силы два провала сила
you call it so and
называешь так и
there for this givenness both lives lead
там за эту данность оба жизни ведут
elections to the
выборы в
Verkhovna Rada I was called there cycles he
верховную раду я там назывался циклах он
checks smoothies  Zheltovskaya USSR bios
проверяет смуси желтовская ссср bios
cunning all i prefer not personality kinases and
хитрым all i prefer не киназы личности и
in Poland the Jedi adopted the bignonia act, that
в польше джедаи приняли акт bignonia то
is, now about galoshes from you can see
есть в ныне про галошами от видно вами
there you haven’t yet asked for
там еще вы не просил еще
her sleeves to the lesson occupied by the
вон ее рукава уроку оккупированные
Roginsky union, but you can’t see the
рогинский союзом а его не видно
zonality or the mare of Latvia should have the
зональность или латвии кобыла должно
sleeves of the lesson, so there are such tees for
рукава урок так что есть такие ти к
walking we have food there, I’m very much
выгулу у нас питания там еще я очень
in the future dishonestly magnificent 91 and
кого в дальше бесчестно пышно 91 так и
there was more domineering  wrote off 95
властное таки было больше списала 95
balls, or what we don’t quite say, we don’t quite
шарик а либо чем что мы на вид не совсем
understand the history of the formation of
скажем разумеем историю формирования
our struggle for the name, we here we
нашей борьбы за называть мы сюда мы
fail the force 90 we plow lessons, we have the right to
провал силы 90 пашем уроки у нас право
force in 90 mutu adopted a
силы в 90 муту приняли декларацию
sales declaration and save from and 90 to the fallen
продажам и сохранит от а 90 падшему
opened if after eco h.  P.  yes, in this in
раскрыл если после эко ч.п. да в этом в
Moscow they are so enraged with the yelling, they
москве так бесят ору у нас
took us for the life of minced meat, he writes that independent lithuania is
приняли за жизнь фарша пишет а что литва
even good
независимая даже хороша литва
independent lithuania and you are slaves in russia like that
независимое а вы в россии рабы как то
is lithuania, it can independently
есть литва она может самостоятельно
decide with whom to be friends with whom it is not friends so
решать с кем дружить кем не дружит так
who to sell to whom not to sell it and
кому продавать кому не продавать это и
there is independence yes we are all
есть независимость да мы все
interconnected in this global world so
взаимосвязаны в этом глобальном мире так
we
мы
exchange goods there technologies but
обмениваемся товарами там технологий но
only you have the right to decide what to
только вы вправе решать что как вам
do but you in Russia don’t understand how
делать но вам в россии это не понять как
you laugh 2 that lithuania is independent so
вы смеетесь 2 что литва независимая так
lithuania is independent and you are slaves of
литва независимо а вы в россии рабы
your regime in russia and  until you understand this,
своего режима и пока вы это не поймете
you will work
вы будете работать
so why did they torture me on the last
так почему меня замучили на прошлом
stream why did they torture me on the last
стриме почему меня замутили на прошлом
stream maxim zelenki didn’t understand the meaning of
стриме максим зеленки не понял смысле
why they muddied me on the last stream
почему у меня замутили на прошлом стриме
and didn’t understand
и не понял
who was muddied above so
кто выше замутили так
ismail khan andrey even a miracle shot I want
исмаил хан андрей даже чудо выстрел хочу
to apply to  be alone confused with
быть apply to be alone с толку с
ukrainian language and tikal ismail khan
украинской мовы и тикал исмаил хан
thank you for trying to write
спасибо тебе что ты попробовал написать
in ukrainian it's okay that i
по украински ничего страшного что я
understand that  then it’s a foreign language for you, so
понимаю что это для тебя чужой язык так
hold on, too, I think that the walls should
держитесь тоже я считаю что стены должны
be free and we should have our own
быть свободными и мы иметь свои
states from this Russian empire this Russian
государства от вот этой российской
empire will fall apart tape with andy Kuban is
империи развалится tape with andy кубань
watching Russia and so on angry
смотрит россия и так дальше angry
intriguer I thought 90 pash and yes there and why
интриган я думала 90 пашем да там и чему
don’t we think that our collapse  union for often
не думаем что наша развал союза по часто
advancing mom so to the
для наступаешь маме так to the
metal and the
metal и
republic together with their struggle for
республики вместе своей борьбой за
calling us and 90 89 life is good on
называешь нас и 90 89 жизнь хороша от
whom life does not depend life is good I
кого не зависит жизнь хороша я вам не
can’t kill you with the concept you want here you
смогу убить понятием вы хотите вот вы
come rub rub so came to a free
пришел rub rub так пришел к свободному
man and says
человеку и говорит
dude  you are not free because you are
чувак ты не свободен потому что ты
dependent on food you are dependent on money you are
зависишь от еды ты зависишь от денег ты
dependent on natural conditions how
зависишь от природных условий какой же
independent you are and you don’t understand that the concept of
ты независим и не понимаешь что понятия
independence is not just that you need to
независимость это не то что тебе нужно
eat work it’s that spent you
кушать работы это та провели ты сам
determine your own destiny you want to go to
определять свою судьбу хочешь идти на
work you go not  you want to go to work you don't
работу идешь не хочешь идти на работу не
go hungry then yes it's your choice
идешь голодаешь тогда да это твой выбор
so you want to be a scientist you will be a scientist
так ты хочешь быть ученым будет ученым
you want to be with the forests be a consequence it's
хочешь быть с лесами будь следствие это
your choice  or you don’t understand
твой выбор вам этого не понять свобода
this freedom is not something that’s in the fridge freedom is
это не то что в холодильнике свобода это
what’s in your head
то что у тебя в голове
like
вот
this I’m ice crystals of the Ural
так я кристаллов льда уральской
Republic well I think it
республики ну я думаю еще
’s not yet these territories maydas in the same
настала не этих территорий майдас в в же
plan here I am in these formats plans will be a
план вот я в этих форматах планы будут
credit note pink  don’t
кредитного пиписка розовый парик еще
give a wig for rent there
напрокат е даёте там башкиры
bashkirs bashkortostan and tatarstan want teeth
башкортостан и татарстан захочет зубы
secretly back republics from blue not
тайку спину республик от синих не
sovereign right
суверенное право
so today we will have
так сегодня у нас будет
roulette so but
рулетка так но
let
давайте
me want to try and I still by
я же хочу попробовать и я все-таки по
right these things for streaming so many
праву эти штуки для стримов так много
times let’s try
раз давайте попробуем
cesar  at a time so
сезар за раз так
their sho who wants to skidata stream
их шо кто захочет skidata стрим
there can be filters mats donat iksha 100
есть можно фильтры маты донатом икша 100
hryvnia both seamlessly dropping into c and b
гривен оба бесшовно выпадая в c и b
air
эфир
now let's try to fix it told about
сейчас попробуем так закрепим поведал о
and let's try to sell loot out of you
и давайте попробую сбывать из вас бабло
how will
как буду millenaire
millenaire you do whatever you want seeing what you
ты всё что захочет видя че ты
are on me  my nerves and equipment can be
мне на мои нервы так и аппаратуру может
handed out for pabrec and even punished from a
за розданы pabrec и даже накажешь от
slave of a shaved string and listen to this
раба побритой струны и послушать этой
as if someone wants discounts and can be given
как что кто-то хочет скидок и дано может
from when you are up to  I’ll jump out on Torquin,
из когда ты дона торквин буду
jump out with such an
выскакивают с таким
abyss of thickets of a test attack on
ты пучину заросли тестовой атаке на
falling download
падающие скачать
yes, I’m like myself,
да я сам себе типа
so let’s try to try 300, that is, a
так что попробуем пытаться 300 то есть
board, yes, you would give it to see it from some dam
доска да ты бы дал из какого-то в дамбе
in general 5 so
повидать она вообще 5 так
ok and
окей и
turn on the tape measure so we  after all, we
в включаем рулеточку так мы все-таки
’ll rise one character and
подымемся одного персонажа и
turn to the span of the wire and
повернемся до размах провод и
put a plus sign who guessed the whole man who’s already playing a mini-roller if I’ll immediately take a new
бачив мини-ролик коли сразу новую сниму
one from the dude and the Chinese Irkutsk
из надо c чувак и китайском иркутской
region, I’m alive in Nizhneudinsk so
области че звидки жив в нижнеудинске так
and then having arrived, a satisfied regional
а потом подъехав довольный областной
center is not given  the beech is right in its north,
центр не данный бук прям своей севере
so it’s shorter, he wants to restore the
так она короче он хочет восстановить
Russian empire and the USSR hello
российскую империю и ссср
than the bottom children’s cartoons of
чем нижнюю детские мультики
everyone it’s
всех
scary to think and you remember I don’t remember
страшно подумать и вы помните не помню
only the city they say Khmelnitsky
только город говорят хмельницкий
about four months ago we fought
месяц где-то четыре назад мы сражались
then no 4 less
то нет 4 меньше
maybe
может
yes that’s how it’s interesting with stones  and
да вот как вот интересно камнями и
opinions now you support it is
мнения вот сейчас вы поддерживаете
forced,
вынужден а
well, let's try the look of gadot
ну давайте испробуем вид гадот
has changed and the fiction has now been 6
изменилась и выдумка вот сейчас уже 6
months  tsev didn’t pass, and we talked with him, then for
месяцев не прошло а мы с ним говорили то
two or three months
два-три месяца
did his
поменялось ли его
opinion about support change?
мнение о поддержке вы не в украине а ну
but what have you
плакатом давай не а вот что что вы за
done for all these months for the war for the
эти все месяцы сделали для войны для
war I work on technology, and that is,
войны работаю по технологии а то есть
so I owe them horror and we have
что я должен им ужас и у нас идет
special military operations going on, I
специальные военные операции я просто я
just thought that you somehow help
просто думал что вы как-то помогаете
your military to these meadows  I
вашим военным чтобы чтобы этих лугам я
probably don’t want to talk about these topics with you
наверно эти темы не хочу с вами
and share my
разговаривать и делиться своими
thoughts, and it won’t be enough just
помыслами и на будет достаточно просто
that I work and pay taxes from the window, the
что я работаю и плачу налоги от окна
whale’s advantage over the victim, also
преимущество кита по жертве еще
drop the charity with us,
сбрасывайте благотворительный у нас
why do you need to know
зачем вам это знать
this
поддерживать может в этом разгоняете
?  since there are no
митинги антигены раз нет никаких
military rallies in court,
митингов военных в суде понапридумывали
they came up with the fact that people are holding a rally here
то что нас тут народ митингует да вот
, and we’re about to throw off Putin, so this is
путина вот-вот уже скинем так нам это
Ukraine, the
украина
number of him himself
число он сам низкий антиверо бы низким
low antivero would be low goods b that it’s true Ukrainians here they are such free years on themselves freely well how to democratically find out yours there I remember in this story I will put you told that your Russian lands were taken away from you Odessa Wednesday yes of course of course it’s interesting but how about you now three months have lived until now visa dislocation switching under in this ti some old ones popped up there we will show important inscription lower succumb to porsche and smoke from the bridge hryvnias removal on the roof panic donat jump and a second at a time kicked out the tsar hello yes like this I’m interested in the military, of course, I’ll honestly say that everyone would stand to find anti-military rallies, I’ll quickly I’ll be with a poster, let’s not, yes, but what have you done for all these months for the war for the war work I pay taxes, and so of course I should not we know the horrors, we have special military operations going on, I just, I just think that you somehow help your united so that these crests, but I probably don’t  I don’t want to
[__] но я наверное эти темы не хочу с
talk with you and share them
вами разговаривать и делиться ими куда
where you and I won’t be enough just that
мы с вами не будет достаточно просто что
I work and pay taxes, but for example,
я работаю и плачу налоги а так например
maybe some of the victims still drop the
может какие-то по жертве еще сбрасывайте
charity since why do you need to
благотворительную раз зачем вам это
know this and just wondering how much people
знать и просто интересно насколько люди
want to support it, maybe in this
хотят поддерживать это может в этом
disperse rallies interventionists since there are
разгоняйте митинги интервенты раз нет
no military rallies in
никаких митингов военных ижевске
Izhevsk they came up with then we have people here to
понапридумывали то у нас тут народ
rally and yes you are about to
митингу и да вы путина вот-вот уже
throw off Putin
скинем
Ukraine
украина
he himself is a low anti-vero would he himself be good
он сам низкий антиверо бы он сам товара
b that it’s true Ukrainians here they are so
b что правда украинцы вот они такие
free bots on themselves freely well, as
свободные ботами на себе свободно ну как
it were democratic  to learn about the ice, yes, I remember
бы демократично узнать о льду да я помню
you told me where I would put it, you
вы там рассказывали где я помещу вы
told me that your
рассказывали что у вас отобрали ваши
Russian lands were taken from you Odessa Wednesday, catch up, of
русские земли одессу среда догони
course, it’s interesting, that’s how you
конечно интересно вот как вот вам сейчас
have now lived for three months without Odessa,
три месяца прожили до сих пор без одессы
how
как
hard it is in your soul,
тяжело на душе
yes, yes, but if so  you will live
ну да есть а если так и будете жить
unknown very very very hard it
безвестные сильно очень-очень тяжело
will not be long how long it is how long
будет не долго осталось как она сколько
let's be a seamstress then stay tell me in the
давайте швея потом остаются подскажите
evening
вечеру
she said
она скажите и прогноз чистки кевин
live and cleansing forecast kevin let's say the rocks are not long left of our childhood they won't take coco and the bitching forecast who's going to reach ivan and take dice la bonne saddens the shoe with amethyst a quick-witted bag of tonsils to sit on the planet there is only shorter and back flames they are shorter blinds forever not so on odessa odes we need to understand also at the silk fork I don’t eat didn’t bring you see you said not long you didn’t long and long this is your understanding of how much butter from 0 to 20 which you yourself don’t know maybe days maybe months maybe years undefined song understood another question and excellent, I just love it when people know the city of everything there for another two months odessa-Kyiv and then in two months to meet and the moon let’s not give a ride with me it’s true so listen you say Ukrainians are free and here’s Percy I hope I don’t know maybe eat different versions version if the anarchists are a question, well, the question is, listen to you in Luhansk in Donetsk, too, Ukrainians live up to absolutely right here  they know
живут до абсолютно верно вот они знаете
about him, too, how free they were that they
о него тоже какие были свободные что
seized freedom from ukraine why did
захватили свободу от украины почему вы
n’t you give a very good question very
не дали очень хорошо вопрос очень
finished last year
завершил прошлый год
here you
вот
need a cool food so
нужна классная питания так
often the Russians manipulate it
часто россиян этим манипулируешь
if you are Ukrainians there not imperials so
если вы там украинцы не имперцы так
why don’t you let luhansk and Donetsk go there
почему же вы не отпускаете там луганск и
so  this is a manipulation that’s
донецк так вот это к манипуляции так
called their annexation their aggression on
названы свою аннексии свою агрессию
our territory so
нашей территории так
matte by the fact that if you don’t
матовый тем что если же вы не имперцы
let the imperials go and so out and absolutely basti
отпустить и так вон и абсолютно басти
change upside down understand this traverse
меняют ног на голову понять это траверс
brother
брат
what did you take that people in Luhansk and and
чего вы взяли что люди в луганске и и
Danetki came freedom from Ukraine
данетки заходили свободу от украины
because they
потому что они
revolted maybe tell me the date of
восстали может быть скажите мне дату
this uprising when the filling is ready the
этого восстания когда начинка готова
uprising
восстание
so it’s hard of course to say well
так вот тяжело конечно сказать ну
let’s say it’s May 9 in Mariupol when a
допустим вот 9 мая в мариуполе когда
policeman was shot there it’s not policemen you
милиционера там не милиционеры вы
look at May 9 it’s with your wife and the policemen
смотрите 9 мая это у жены и милиционеры
you were giving I’ll answer you then
вы были давать я вам отвечу значит
look  from April 12, 2014, you
смотрите с 12 апреля 2014 года просто вы
just start right away with the armor of the fuss, no, I'm
сразу начинайте с броня суеты нет еще я
correcting yours again to me  On May 12, they accepted on
ваш поправляю еще раз мне 12 приняли 5
May 5, they appointed police officers on May 1, and I
мая поставили милиционеров 1-го мая и
answer questions because April 12
вопросам отвечаю потому что 12 апреля
goes until May 9, so we want to understand it
идет до 9 мая так мы хотим понять его
.  I looked absolutely at my leisure
видео есть посматривал абсолютно досуге
April 12, 2006, a detachment of Russian
12 апреля 2006 года отряд российских
militants under the command of Girkin
боевиков под командованием гиркина
Rifle You know such a character
стрелкового знаете такого персонажа
profitability captured the city of Slavyansk,
доходность захватили город славянск
it was exactly April 12 that it was
точно это в апреле было 12 апреля точно
clear that if you could
понятно что при можете проводилась мне
trust me tender and for the first time I will voice
доверять нежную и первый раз озвучу
from that moment and the occupation of
с этого момента и началась оккупация
this audience began
этой аудитории
lived announced I heard you
прожила объявлял слышу я услышал ваш
rejected then it turns out we are defending ourselves
отверг тогда получается мы обороняемся
from you so then you are
от вас так то вы
Russia how to defend yourself not for a gift but
россия как обороняйтесь не на подарок а
in the ninety-fifth year
в девяносто пятом году
Sasha white still comrades like Kachinsky
сашка белый еще товарищи типа качинского
attacked us Chechnya will not
напали на нас чечне не станет
who look in Chechnya there was a legitimate
кто смотрите в чечне была легитимное
government
правительство
what was Chechnya  declared
что было давайте чечня провозгласила
its independence
свою независимость
in what year and
в каком году и
in  t we smoothly crossed the totems of Chechnya, more often than not
вот мы плавно перешли тотемы чечне дуже
, Russia will punish your militants there, they
часто россия накажет вот ваши там
came to Chechnya, then my
боевики приезжали в чечню то моего этом
pictures of white Sasha,
картинки белый сашка
we drink on the move to Bezhitsky, no matter what, she’s
мы пить ходом до бежицкого бы то ни она
on a patch without a rumble cool and failure, the force
на патчить без гула cool и провал сила
went wrong chechnya
не заладились чечня
write when chechnya declared
напишите когда чечня провозгласила
independence
независимость
write your own  version and you help, this is
напишите свою версию и вы помощи это
also access to get and who
тоже доступ достать и кого
will you be from dubov not alla chechnya
вы будет с дубова не алла чечня
voted hostage earlier for ukraine to the
проголосовано заложник раньше за украину
act and also so far it seems about chechnya in what
акту и тоже пока вроде о чечне в каком
year chechnya proclaimed regardless of who
году чечня провозгласила независимо кто
confirmed it the supreme council of chechen
это подтвердил верховный совет чеченской
no no no must some country not
нет нет нет должно какая-то страна не
protection proclaimed let's wait
защите провозгласила подождем
proclaimed yes in what year to heal that's
провозгласила да в каком году зажить вот
who who will live this year
кто ли кто это проживет в этом году
proclaimed who confirmed it I
провозгласила кто это подтвердил я
generally rush what year
вообще rush каком году провозгласила
Chechnya declared independence no you are coming to
чечня независимость нет вы съезжаетесь
embellish and I just want no me
приукрасить и просто я хочу нет меня
let's do it
давайте то
even before the collapse of the Soviet Union full
еще до развала советского союза полного
so Chechnya  proclaimed don't depend on you
так чечня провозгласила не зависит вы
wait we don't move out or militants your
подождите мы не съезжайте or боевики ваш
once again milking  I’ll tell you our calls with
еще раз дояра вам расскажу наши звонки с
whom you fought in Chechnya
кем вы воевали в чечне
with someone militants you fought with the
с кем-то боевиками вы воевали с
officially elected authorities of the Chechen
официально избранными властями чеченской
Republic was Dudarev Dudayev was yes
республики был дударев дудаев был да
where did he come from a few days before his
откуда он за несколько дней до его
wrong Dudayev was there in the morning there
неправильно дудаев был там утром много
were a lot of militants us Afghans in the countries badge
было боевиков нас афгане в странах жетон
with  afghanistan, too, let's now
с афганистаном тоже давай сейчас
look, let's see Dudayev was the
смотрите давайте так дудаев был
official elected leader of
официальным избранным руководителем
Chechnya without a clue there were elections there was a
чечней без понятия были выборы был были
choice or a choice and yes let's see
выбор или выбор и да давайте посмотрим
they called you look at the computer just
назвали просмотрите вас компьютер просто
talk and there was no
говорите и не был
parliament of the freudian republic to know them
был парламент фрейда республики знать их
90 even open so interesting
90 даже откроется так интересно
they didn't make the computer crash  I’m
не заставили компьютеру падает я сейчас
going to open it myself, wait, I
вы сами будете открывать подождите я сам
’ll take a look together raised
посмотрю вместе повысили
[music]
[музыка]
anna malysheva
анна малышева
anna malysheva asks in chat she doesn’t
анна малышева спрашивает в чате она не
understand how online I put a person
понимает как онлайне я ставлю человека
on pause anna malysheva and the tigers are not a doctor
на паузу анна малышева и тигры не медик
people to
принятые сейчас из 100 ватт и людей на
pause and
паузу и
raise the hryvnia to the intellect tedx who
поднимать гривен интеллекту tedx кто
disappears
девается стёр
erased  t declared independence Bewley 91
вот провозгласила независимость бьюли 91
the first president was Dzhokhar
года первым президентом стал джохар
Dudayev
дудаев
ninety-third was Pauline and
девяносто третьем была полина и
if we are talking about Chechnya Mutu there were
если мы говорим про чечню муту там были
official authorities elected by the population
официальные власти избранные населением
and they proclaimed it does not depend on
и они провозгласили не зависит
if we are talking about Chechnya ninety-
если мы говорим про в чечне девяносто
first year there were elections really on
первом году были выбора действительно 27
October 27 and
октября а
if we  we are talking about an analogy if you want there
если мы говорим про аналогию хотите там
Donetsk lugansk it is in Donetsk lugansk not
донецк луганск это в донецке луганске не
only a friend of the Zhiguli of choice no look not the
одни друга жигули выбора нет смотри не
Lugansk regional council not the Donetsk
луганский областной совет не донецка
ambassador the world did not proclaim any DPR
посла свет не провозглашали никакие днр
where did these genes come from
откуда взялись эти гены
independence the
независимость
referendum took place what and who
референдум проходил что а кто кто
organized a variable referendum on the
организовывал переменную референдум по
referendum during the fighting
референдуму же во время боевых действий
I went through one of the actions from the volume and that
один из тома я проходил и что
where did the Donetsk People's Republic come from,
откуда взялась донецкая народная
which led the legend who
республика которая проводила легенду кто
led where to him, but the music of the authorities of the
проводил где нему но музыка власти
republic and the authorities of the authorities themselves failed
республики и власти власть сама провал
to defeat, that is, it means that the republic
на поражение то есть значит республика
appeared dory the film and left again,
появилась дори фильм и опять ушли
look
смотрите
here to eavesdrop if
здесь подслушать если здесь заходит
Girkin enters here, this is very good  it’s really bad and we’re at war with
гиркин это очень плохо и мы воюем с
russia if it comes here
россией если тут заходит соску билось к
it’s nip to the russians we’re not at war with ukraine we
российским мы не воюем с украиной мы
’re at war anyway with
воюем все равно с чеченской республикой
the chechen republic
республики были официальные власти
like it’s your
которые и против которых вы его есть они
job  Ukraine’s official request
сделали официальный запрос украины
blew a screen despite Sashka Bella
дохнула экраном несмотря сашка беллы
Korchinsky and the volunteers they
корчинский да и добровольцы они
participated on the side of the
участвовали на стороне
official authorities and not some
официальных властей а не каких-то
militants, that is, the Chechen
боевиков то есть то есть чеченская
Republic, headed by Dzhokhar Dudayev,
республика во главе с джохаром дудаевым
made an official request to Ukraine and
сделал официальный запрос в украину и
Ukraine gave the go-ahead to go
украина дала добро отправилась в
voluntarily to another state
добровольно другом рамках государства
it’s very so, maybe it’s also flexible and
очень так вот может и гибким тоже добра
kind, but who did it, yes, just if that’s how
вот а кто сделал да просто если так уж я
I say that look, they just said what
и говорю что смотрите сказали только что
it means voluntarily, but here you need
там значит добровольно а здесь надо
to make a request yes no again you
делать запрос да нет еще раз вы вы
are running away now, look now I agreed with you
сейчас убегаете смотри теперь я с вами
good at the novel
согласился доброго у романа помощь
Girkin came to help who is not indifferent,
пришел гиркин кому не безразлична вот
it was he who came voluntarily not  just
именно он пришел добровольно не только
came as 8 he started the war he started the
пришла как 8 он начал войну он начал
war started the war that is, it’s like
войну начал войну то есть это как
Munchausen
мюнхаузен
absolutely all I declare war on England
абсолютно весь я объявляю войну англии
before that you can see your words
до этого можно вас ваших слов смотрите
like this, that is, I now declare war on
так то есть я сейчас объявляю войну
Great Britain and let’s say if I
великобритании и вот допустим если я
start to fight swing legalize for another two hours
начинаю воевать свинг еще два часа
chechnya war chechnya was the
легализовать чечне война чечне был
official leadership of
официальное руководство
russia there is no big difference and i say
россии нет большая разница и я говорю
she made a request to ukraine is absolutely
она делала запрос украину абсолютно
impossible she asked he taught me and
невозможно она просила он учил и мне
then talk about it
тогда про это говорить потому что
because you see because i
смотрите вы потому что что мне есть
was
официально была
officially catching the official for helping stuffing was
ловлю официального за помог набивай было
not interrupting you pick up  then
не перебивайте вы подбираете значит
look they are under the mountain of peace, the issue does not burn out
смотри они под гора мира не подгорает
, you change pairs Dudayev was the
выпуск вы меняете пар дудаев был
official president of the republic there are
официальным президентом республики есть
glasses of the republic’s parliament and that in the
парламент республики очки и что вы
ninety-third year you fought with the
девяносто третьем году ок воевали с
free republics recognized as absolutely democratic elected government
выбранной властью свободный республик
if you were volunteers from Ukraine
если вы и до были добровольцы из украины
who fought on the side of this  in
которые воевали на стороне этой в
illegal from the point of view of Ukrainian  if
незаконно с точки зрения украинского
you want to transfer the analogy to
при хотите перенести аналогию на донецк
Donetsk-Luhansk, then whom
луганск то кому пришел
did the Donetsk
гибким помогать не донецкий областной
Regional Council come to help
областной совет не принимали не какие
flexible?  you didn’t fight
решения при не зависит и не не воевали
for some, you don’t notice, you know about he
за какую-то не замечаешь знаете о
came up to help someone, but these
подошел помогает кому-кому а вот этим
demonstrations by thousands of people who
демонстрации многотысячным которые с
still consider one to two with Russian flags
русскими флагами еще рассмотреть один к
and when he came he came to the city of
двум и когда пришел он пришел на город
Slavyansk
славянск например захватил так сместил
it’s 52, here’s 50
сколько еще сначала пришло 52 вот 50
people, you can find out the Slavic population,
человека можно узнать население
like 100,000 was 100,000, how
славянская вроде 100000 было 100000 как
can 50 people capture a hundred thousandth
может 50 человек захватить стотысячный
race,
гонка
how many people captured in Budyonnovsk
сколько человек захватила в будённовске
captured that we have been assigned a month and
захватила что месяц у нас возложена и
led the hospital or the sick hospital in
вели больницу или больным больницу
Budyonnovsk to the hospital to be equipped with what it is
будённовске до больницы оснащаться чем
now comparing it’s impossible to first head
сейчас сравнивая нельзя сначала главе
still captured and  sickness  what difference does it make
еще захватили и больницу в будет какая
what difference does it make to look at the difference in the
разница какая разница смотреть разница в
camera today they captured them first
камере сегодня на захватила они сначала
you seriously chala absolutely seriously
вы серьезно чала абсолютно серьезно
before the leaves cried waiting with
перед тем листья наплакал ожидании со
your friends giving nerds ribbons
своими друзьями дав ботаны лентами
grenades and a hundred thousandth gate
гранатами и ворот стотысячный
you are absolutely in your power before that is
вы в себе абсолютно в силе до то есть у
you have a large group there  troops stood
вас там большая группировка войск стояла
there the
там
police questions you just say
полиции вопросов вам просто сказать
nothing why you how good 10 people
ничего а почему вы как хорошо 10 человек
can capture 100 thousand how many
может захватить 100 тысяч сколько
people how many thousand how many people in
человек сколько-то тысяч сколько чения в
1000 city of policemen tell me how many
1000 городе милиционеров скажите сколько
people the music of ukraine is on pebbles and you need a
человек музыка украины на гальке а нужно
person in your opinion to capture the city of
человек по вашему чтобы захватить город
whom food in  mix you two Russian
кого питания в миксе вы две российские
propaganda checks as well as 52 people
пропаганда чеки также как 52 человека
can capture the city you are so
может захватить город вы что так
attached I ask logically because then how many
привязаны задаю логично потому а сколько
people do you think are enough to
тогда по вашему людей достаточно чтобы
capture the city here is the set I action these
захватить город вот набор я экшн эти
people are real ju 52
люди настоя ju 52
people we can buy both
человека мы можно купить и места
construction sites and to the deep  it's not me but
строительства и to the deep это не я а
squid and
squid и 53 54-я к его оценка и вот
53  araz vin tell
такого напишите скелете зараз вин скажи
me what this people can buy
мне какие this людей может уде закупает
and places so write it yes this
и места так напишите это да вот этот
guy thinks that 52 people
паренек так он считает что 52 человека
can’t capture the city I’ll ask
не может захватить город я спрошу а
how many then can and that’s how much he
сколько тогда может и вот сколько он
now named logically if he thinks
сейчас назвали логично если он считает
that 52 can’t mean  somewhere in
что 52 не может значит он где-то в
his head he has an idea how many people
голове имеет понятие сколько человек
can capture the prize the concept if you have no
может захватить приз понятие если вы без
idea how do you know that 52 is not
понятие откуда вы знаете что 52 не
enough for this I’m just
хватает для этого мне вот просто
wondering how much and where are you again
интересно сколько а вы где еще раз
let’s say again and there are already
допустим еще раз и есть городе уже
policemen in the city you say I don’t know
милиционеров вы говорите я не знаю
how many
сколько
you are at least two hundred, I think exactly
вы не меньше двухсот думаю точными
how 50 people could just take it and
как 50 человек могло вот просто взять и
disrupt it like
сорвать как на автоматическим оружием
there is no center on automatic weapons, why not baths and
центр не бывает почему не бани и
promotions and because so
повышением и потому что так что почему
why not maybe you could you
бы не возможно бывает вас могли вы вы
do something you don’t  sometimes the
делаете какое-то вы что так не бывает
mass was equal to Budyonnovsky and
масса равнялась буденновском да
absolutely a build-up of absal before
абсолютно наростом абсаль до людей
peaceful people simply took hostage
мирных просто взяли в заложники
colleagues
коллег
captured the valley called look,
захватили долина позвал посмотрите
for example,
например
look after the capture  slavyansk generally
смотрите после захвата славянска вообще
wait for wearing a geyr aristo the
подожди ща носящий гейр aristo на
next day yes yes the prosecutor general’s office
следующий день да да генпрокуратура
follow the contour that the guards ok
следовать контуру которые охраны ок
kindly knew I you 3 broke the ventru
добрый знал я вам 3 разбил вентру
culture wedge ask again who
культуру клин спросить еще раз кто
recognized to
признал
work out a single service saying the
выработать единую службу говоря на
next day or two days before
следующий день или через два дня до
after saturation until after the capture of
после насыщения до после захвата
slavyansk
славянска
we captured Gorlovka and
захватили горловку и
a city council member we raised the
депутата городского совета мы подняли
Russian flag a city
российский флаг депутат городского
council member an officially elected resident of
совета официально избранный житель
Gorlovka took off this Russian flag
горловки взял снял этот российский флаг
and hung the Ukrainian flag back, so they
и повесил назад украинский так что с ним
made him be Russian on it until they
сделали быть по ней российский до
ripped open his stomach and threw him into the river and
вспороли ему живот и выкинули в речку а
look at the murder of Vladimir the fisherman
посмотрите убийство владимира рыбака
look
посмотри
carefully  and sent people yours left
хорошенько и слали людей ваш ушло когда
when 50 people entered there, and where how many
вот туда вошло 50 человек а куда сколько
went before the finals left because why
ушло до финала ушел потому что почему
why because because Russia from Russia
почему потому что россии из россии
absolutely laugh at night let's get to
абсолютно ржешь на ночь давайте так
know and sha1
откуда взялся знать и sha1
propagandistic Russian such massage
пропагандистский российский такие массаж
if Girkin went in 52 why did it go there a
если гиркин зашел 52 почему ушло там
little  ain't a thousand so type it n  why
чуть ли не тысячи так типа его почему
so won’t they be afraid instead of them, in short,
так воны типа не боится вместо их короче
there thousands took so ville of pure people
там тыщ взялась так ville чистых люда
it was all nodding and militants,
это была вся кивать и боевики то
motorolas are shorter than a woman and every trophy
моторолы короче бабой и всякая трофейный
clinic came from Russia and so it came
клиника пришла с руси и так и приходила
and the arrival of satoshi zahids 52 as in the
и прихода сатошей захидов 52 как в той
same further added and then  how are the
же дальше добавилась и тогда как тут
backgrounds with a view of the excellent maniple 2nd
фоны с видом отлично манипуле 2-ой
motorola
motorola
where did this time not local on the
откуда взялся этот раз не местных на
naked motorola come from as a volunteer
голом motorola приехал добровольцем
still got rich and the brain
еще разжился а мозговой
don’t run away look our barely breathing waka
не убегайте смотрите наш еле дышит вака
laboratory assistants there was yes where did
лаборантов есть было да откуда взялись
all these papers of the Cossacks come from were a
эти все бумаги казачества были были
scientist such a [ __ ] as a person a [ __ ]
ученый такой [__] как человек дебильное
face such as they entered 50 left
лицо такое как они вошли 50 ушли из
only now they were going because it’s not like that
только вот они шли потому что ж не так
you said that  I captured 50 absolutely the
вы ж сказали что захватила 50 абсолютно
size of the vein and then don’t say
размер вены и дальше да не надо говорить
that I’m doing moronic things, do it if there’s
что я делаю дебильные делайте вот если
an absolute thing that I can, I’m looking at  professor,
абсолютного что смогу я смотрю профессор
I’m not saying that you are morons the game that you are
я же не говорю что вы [__] игру что вы
making a moronic face how to understand how to
делаете дебильное лицо как как понять
make death with such questions it
делать гибель такими вопросами это
showed here you understand the way out
показывал вот вы понимаете выхода
to say this you have to insert a word to the commune,
говорить это у вас к коммуне слово
you don’t understand the tactics of the
вставить не даете понимаю тактики
moment you talk nonsense and understand
момента вы бред говорить и понимаете еще
again my nonsense ransom  people people on the
раз мой бред выкуп люди люди на
territory of the Donetsk luhansk region
территории донецкой луганской области
lived in peace so that there were no
жили себе спокойно дабы не было
small shoots who wanted
небольшое побеги которые хотели зараза
to bomb the infection did not start tell me when we
бомбить не начали скажите когда мы
started to bomb now tell me when they started
начали бомбить вот скажите когда начали
to bomb us well yes Tuska resident will say
бомбить нас хорошо да туска житель скажу
well let's guess I Kazakh will be the date
ну давайте угадаете я казах будет дата
when they started bombing Donetsk luhansk  it
когда начали бомбить донецк луганск это
’s interesting that the militants of the
за интересно получается что и боевики
esophagus can also start bombing there, no,
пищевода можно начали бомбить там нет ну
well, almost their own version, when they started
на почти свою версию когда же начали
bombing Donetsk
бомбить донецк луганск
Luhansk mitiko, but
митико а
I’m wondering before the
вот мне интересно до того как боевики
Russian militants came, someone with an eyebrow, yes no,
российские пришли кто-то бровью да нет
calm down and for the head’s son, don’t ashanti,
успокойтесь и за сын главы не ashanti
let’s go  how flexible came
давайте до того как гибким пришла 12
April 12 began you can be silent
апреля началась вы можете помолчать
took this minute you can menu broadcast
принял эту минуту можно меню эфир
filled in vocabulary here is verbal
заполненного словарный вот словесный
diarrhea, perhaps,
понос возможно возможно у вас
by bombarding your brain a little
по бомбардируя ваш мозг немножко там
, something will be deposited there, maybe a grain of some kind of
что-то отложится может зерно какое-то
exercise from a puddle
упражнение от лужица
that you tell me no, there is such a brain
что вы мне говорите нет есть такой мозг
that it does not report anything from
что в него что не докладывать о ничего
anywhere, it is such a
ниоткуда не откладывается бывает такой
listen, well  let's say 5
слушайте ну вот допустим 5
to 13 August top and again we will start on
по 13 августа топ а еще раз мы начнем 12
August 12 on April 12 I say 13 and on
августа 12 апреля говорю 13 а в 12
April 12 there was something quite a lot 13 the same
апреля было что-то немало 13 это же
war was a war on lacquer okay, that is,
война шла война по лаковой ладно то есть
if there is a war, consider it to take and
если идет война рассмотреть это брать и
shoot planes daddy yesterday zur  once
стрелять самолетами папуля вчера зур еще
again we are looking from c to find a Russian horror story
раз ищем от c найти российская страшилка
that Ukraine took and just, like, launched an
что украина взяла и просто типа нанесла
airstrike on the beach with children, so this is
авиаудар по пляжу детьми так это еще
another huge fairy that
один к огромнейший фей который
Russian propaganda spreads,
распространяет российская пропаганда как
imagine watching like it, let's
ты представьте следят понравится давайте
bang just shorter there on the beach with
бахнем просто короче там по пляжу с
children on the
детьми
plane at first this version was that
самолету сначала эта версия была что
the airstrike then realized that in short it doesn’t
авиаудар потом поняли шо короче она не
stick already 2 only artillery
клеится уже 2 лишь артиллерийский
shelling and so on so this is also
обстрел и так дальше так вот это также
like ro  Russia is now shelling
как россия сейчас обстреливается mode
this Zaporizhzhya nuclear power plant, so during
эту запорожского атомную станцию так во
the arrival of the muzzle, and there they seem to have
время приезда морды и там вроде как бы
neutralized 60 Ukrainian saboteurs,
нейтрализовали 60 украинских диверсантов
but it’s a miracle that not one saboteur was
но чуда не одного диверсанта нет из тех
sunk on
потопили на
this Russia, this country is fake, she makes
это россия это страна фейк она делает
special these freaks even at the cost of
специальные вот эти фрики даже ценой
killing people, and if we  we remember how
убийство людей и если мы помним как
Putin came to power so these explosions
путин пришел к власти так вот эти взрывы
in the Russian cities of Volgodonsk so
в российских городах волгодонске так
on so that is the
дальше так то есть это
country this regime is built on murders
страна этот режим построен на убийствах
and terrorist attacks drinking it is not on this
и терактах пить дело не на этом
intimidation of the
запугивание населения
population again means until April 12 before the invasion of the
еще раз значит до 12 апреля до вторжения
Russians there were some kind of
россиян были какие-то
fences by whom  -something else before April 12th
ограждениям кем-то еще до 12-го апреля
so that they would plant what you were,
чтобы чтобы подсаживали что вы было был
let's be so binary for you until April 12th there
давайте так бинарный для вас до 12
were some kind of hostilities in the
апреля были какие-то боевые действия на
Luhansk region
луганской области
fighting in Donbass
апреля были какие-то на донбассе боевые
yes or no
да или нет
it works yes so work until the 12th of
это работает да так работы до 12-ого
yours I'm not going to dance to your tune here
вашего я под вашу дудочку тут плясать не
google is already  let’s go to the beach until
собирается google уже пляжике давайте до
April 12, so that later until April 12 I still
12 апреля чтоб потом до 12 апреля я еще
broke it, they also said that Russia until
разбил еще рассказали что россия до 12
April 12, Otranto region 12, there was no friction
апреля область 12 отранто были ни трения
, Donbass was added again, and therefore I’m
добавила донбасс и поэтому пришло я вас
asking you until April 12, some kind of
спрашиваю до 12 апреля какие-то боевые
hostilities were on the territory of the concept without
действия были на терере понятие без
there was no idea, we will fix the seams,
понятия не было ни мы зафиксируем швы
there would be no record yet, there is still no need to
было был бы нет записи еще не надо еще
do anything else, which means I didn’t say that it would be in the
дела значит я не говорил что будет в
filling until 12 yet, they brought this thesis
начинку до 12 еще на вывели этот тезис
until April 12, no hostilities by the
до 12 апреля никаких боевых действий
sky, I said sunbathing on April 12 and look at the
небом я сказала загорание 12 апреля и на
table first, type  concepts
стол смотрите сначала наберитесь понятий
and then go to the roulette but just gave
и тогда заходите в рулетку а только дал
me you without a clue and look at such an
мне вы без понятия и осматривают такое
education absolutely naked two
образован абсолютно оголенного два
higher educations up to higher 1 before it
высших образования до высших 1 до это ни
’s not a programmer you can buy them you
о чем не программист ими можно купить
can buy yes you who by
можно купить да вот вы кто по
education
образованию
don’t want
не хочу
[music]
[музыка]
nobody  bought but didn’t receive money,
никого не купили да не получил денег это
now we’ll be back, look that even to
вот вернемся смотрите что даже на
Ukraine 12 floors until April 12 there are no
украину 12 этажей до 12 апреля никаких
hostilities and you still know how to choose
боевых действий а вы еще умеете к выбору
mid 12 to can chewing you can  help her.
мида 12 до могу жуя вы можете помочь ей
for to give but said give
звуки уже для для дачи но сказал дайте
accents to find in the mouth swear that i want
акценты найти во рту swear that i want
to go out to say there bombed
to кто-то вон идти в скажем там бомбили
bombed so that is, imagine
бомбили так то есть представьте такой
this one specially in Russian so that
вот специально по-русски чтобы нас
people from other countries of the us of russia
услышали люди из других стран еэс россии
could hear us whether the council and the union bombed stalingrad
бомбил ли совет и союз сталинград
it’s natural that when hostilities were going
естественно что когда шли боевые
on, including the
действия так в том числе
building, people suffered from the guns of the
строение люди страдали от орудий
Soviet Union, too, because this
советского союза тоже потому что эта
war, if Russians are standing in Stalingrad,
война если сталинграде стоят российские
you will say
вы скажете светки
German troops are shining, so it’s natural that
немецкие войска так то естественно что
during the battles for Stalingrad ours will be
во время боев за сталинград наш будут
some victims, there will be destruction,
некоторые жертвы цвели будут разрушений
but who is to blame  shelling of stalingrad the
но кто виноват обстрелах сталинграда
soviet union which something there
советский союз который что-то там
fired at german guns which
стрелял по немецким пушкам которые были
were or the germans who captured d  about the
ли или немцы которые захватили до
territory with and so the very thing here, that is, it
территорию с а так самое тут то есть
turns out that the Russian army,
получается что российская армия
through its proxies and regulars, can
через своих прокси и регулярка может
enter and stand, do not shoot from there,
заходить и стоять не стрелять оттуда так
and the Ukrainian cannot advance, since
и продвигаться украинская не может так
it is eight years old
как обстреливать в восемь лет восемь лет
that the Ukrainian army cannot shell some unfortunate
так украинская армия каких-то несчастных
miners with slingshots  could not
шахтеров с рогатками не могла не могла
hold it back, and now when the Russian army rushed to her
сдержать а теперь когда ломанулась ей на
aid, so the
помощь российская армия так что
Russian army cannot
российская армия не может с этими
move further with these miners, yes,
шахтерами продвинуться дальше да там на
there must not be repaired, it didn’t affect
этом надо не чинить надо не сказалось
somehow interesting some kind of
как-то интересно какие то шахтеры
keepass miners with slingshots cyborgs were
keepass рогатками киборги были на
probably
наверно
there  we have a
есть такая у нас
worthy story here is Allah himself ashati
история достойно вот аллах сам ашати
whom are you dude prices he sits in Irkutsk
кого ты чувак цены он сидит иркутские
moved from the bottom at the Dinskaya cycle
переехал с нижней у динская цикле
zazhopinsk such as pleases that he
зажопинске такие как радует то что он
arrived dangerous center o he was nowhere
приехал опасный центр о он не был нигде
but russia with the previous role the same
кроме россии с предыдущим роли тем же
he talked englin days in russia well
ним общались энглин дней в россии хорошо
there  we have so much
там у нас тут столько природы
nature here  will soon capture addison sit
скоро вот он скоро захватит addison сиди
there in the background of your candle and capture
там на фоне своего свеча и захватывает
odessa on the
одесса на
power deck before
деке питания до
trying alexander as a cadet by the way
пытаюсь александр кадетом кстати
I asked something wrong I’m catching up in
спрашивал я что то не так догоняю в
russia is there no choice go to work
россии разве нет выбора иди на работу
or don’t go go study there or it doesn’t
или не иди иди учиться туда-то или не
matter there is some kind of freedom  and restrictions in the
беда есть некая не свобода и ограничения
political sense, but only in this way, just in
политическом смысле но и только так вот
this way, the restriction in the political
именно так ограничение политическом
sense, you Alexander can
смысле вы александр можете
be elected in the elections to be elected and
избираться на выборах быть избранным и
are you honestly guaranteed this choice, I
гарантируется ли вам честно этот выбор я
think that no, I think that if you come
думаю что нет я думаю что если вы
out with some kind of political
выйдете с какими-то политической своей
program of your own, then you will very soon
программы так вы очень скоро
change your impudent you as if there
измените свои дерзкие вы словно там
is something that is wrong in russia with freedom
что-то что не так в россии со свободно
before you are allowed to work you are allowed to
до вам разрешают работы вам разрешаю там
eat there but that's all
кушать есть но это все
you are allowed to use material
вам разрешают пользоваться материальными
wealth so but to decide the distribution of
благами так вот но решать распределение
material wealth that is, you cannot participate in the
материальных благ то есть участвуют в
political life of the state
политической жизни государства вам
as  if Oleg Proshin doesn’t talk about this now, he
нельзя как бы в этого сейчас не
is
рассказывает
Andrey on May 2, it’s more important to
олег прошин он андрей мая 2 за важнее на
bother explaining them  of the
заморачивайтесь разъяснять их из фактов
qing facts in the yards, no one was low enough,
цин по дворам никто хватало низкий
I’ll get up a pill, only to joke with you, not a
встану таблетку только с вами шукать не
video, I explain the facts on for the
видео я разъясняю факты на для цик
pathword cic, but for those who
pathword а для тех кто слуха богатую
hear the rich daiki, that is, meditation is the facts, that
daiki слушают то есть раздумие факты то
is, it is necessary to tell the size of the requirement
есть надо кинца разме треба разъясняет
from the slave, we here personally know how to  4 teaches
от раба мы тут лично знаю как в 4 учит
cast iron about the view of Klaus at two or three times and
литой чугун о вид клаус у раз два три и
in but the view of where you are so
в но вид куда ты так
letting Dasha go The war began to hide it Yes,
пущу дашу война началась скрывать это да
and what shall we say in Donetsk, the Luhansk
и что мы скажем по донецку луганскую
region, it must be emphasized that there were no
область надо акцентировать что никаких
hostilities in the Donbass
боевых действий на донбассе
before the arrival of armed formations from them
до прихода из них вооруженных
let
формирований не было так давайте я царь
me be the tsar, I have
мне предстоит
to thank you for the stream and it sounds
да спасибо за stream так и звучит
cool
прикольно
evgenia vilnius and from
евгения вильнюс а из вильнюса
vilnius I sound to give and the donators were and
это я звучу дать и донатики был и пришли
they just came like this
они просто ховалась так
[music]
[музыка]
I’m a tobacco company a little shaved often
я компания табачной чуть побритая часто
well the text and the name of yashin and having sorted it out usually
ну тексту и имени яшин и разобрав обычно
setting up the site  Ali directly brings
настроив сайт али прям на приношу
donations and so we sort it
донат и так и
out on a new microphone
разбираем на новый микрофон
monetization is disabled click monetization
монетизация отключена монетизация клик у
I had conclusions on the price of the army so for
меня было выводами на цена армию так за
divorce  ohm, in a month, monetization will turn on, I
разводом через месяц включится
’ll give out, but punish from, but the cotton wool envelope of the
выдам но наказать из но конверт ваты
army, however, we’ll try now and
армии однако будем сейчас пробовать и
I want a normal pipe studio, you and stupidly
хочу нормальную студию трубе ты и глупо
staggering rock fought prophecy on and
шатается скалу бились prophecy на и
let’s turn to our rubric without
давайте повернемся до нашей рубрике без
Google, so for a second we have the ethics of dad’s
гугла так секунду у нас этика вещи папы
thing, or is it me
то ли на это я
[music]
[музыка]
about lithuania i
про литву
want to cut it down so put a plus
хочу срубит это так вот поставьте плюс
who knows the lithuanian language of memes then
кто из вас знает литовский язык мемов то
they don’t know put a plus who knows the
не знают поставьте плюс кто знает
lithuanian language and minuses who don’t know
литовскую мову а минусы кто не знает
writes before they glorify having removed youtube there is a
пишет до они славлю сняв youtube есть
video about the beach and the rest you can
видео про пляж и остальные можете их
bypass them nothing  to discuss the beach, that is,
обходить не что обсуждать пляж то есть
if you see the beach and the arrival of
если вы видите пляж и прилет удары
some kind of hail strikes there, only oh, so what
каких-то там градами лишь о так что это
does it mean that hail flew to the beach,
значит это значит что на пляж прилетели
there is no evidence that it
града никакого доказательства что это
took and Ukraine fired,
брало и украина обстреливала нету но
but there is a video when the militants themselves
зато есть видео то когда боевики сами
laid out how they were with  hail on two
выкладывали как они с градов на две
sides to shoot this one, you can
стороны стрелять этой эти можете
look and think what is where they
посмотреть и подумать что такое где же
don’t stand against anyone not on two sides with
не стоят против кого не на две стороны
hail so they still laugh and
градами так еще смеются и
under  think about who would benefit from
подумайте кто кому выгодно было
shelling civilians here from people in
обстреливать мирных вот от людей для
order to
того чтобы
educate and incite hatred for
воспитывать и возбуждать ненависть к
Ukraine
украине
ok let's let's go around the edges of such a
ok давайте давайте мы по краям такую
group with guess a melody up with guess
group with гадай мелодию up with гадай
words so at a time we are not infantry in a pharmacy
слова так за раз мы не пехоту в аптеке
words have grown to the river Lithuanian words and beyond
слова дорос до реки литовски слова и за
since we will be him and mom gratis such an
раз мы будем он с мамой gratis такая
infection the growth of a fish so that you
зараза рост рыба чтобы вы
I camera for the dates second
я камеру за даты секунду
1 point for the delivery
1 очко за доставку
[music]
[музыка]
let's play with him like that for a second
давайте так поиграемся с его секунду
I didn't even think about it, well, it looks like it
я не подумал даже у ну так на вида
settles down about
обживается об
just a glinka happiness and
просто глинка счастье и
so here it is  the words and who we will guess
так вот же перше слова и кем мы угадаем
for the
за
Lithuanian new
литовской новые
attacks on pushing on your idea what it
атаки на пушить на вашу думку що воно
means
означает
at a discount in us today friendly outskirts of
по скидке в нас сегодня дружной окраина
d 2 we stream dishes from each of us pleases and
д 2 мы каждому стриме блюдам из радует и
brushes to the wreaths of Crimea friendly to us and here in
кисти к венки дружных нам крым и вот по
Lithuania we will try it with us
литве мы попробуем это у нас
Indo-European move  it mind
индоевропейских move it уму
sounding boards where words are similar try to guess the
деки слова где схожи попробуйте угадать
sonorous what you know here are the words blocks don’t
звучное что знаете вот слова блоки не
know the right choice so
знаете правильный выбор так
I’ll say the data is brave this still even rows of
скажу данные бравый this таки дуже рядки
words to the water and
слова к воде и
at a time we give in  I’m someone so
за раз мы поддаёмся кто видов так
let’s
давайте
give, that is, give
давать то есть давать
you a vsky sea of the word give and give to but t
вы-то вский море слова давать и давать в
e Ukrainian special forces from the Russian so-an
но спецназ украинскую из российской
-so c1 Indo-
так-то c1
uropean Indian family lightning put a
индоевропейским индийской молнии семьи
plus sign then a kind of reptiles and a minus in tons
поставьте плюсик то вид гадов а минус в
type of reptiles and go to another word
тонны вид гадов и переходом до другого
ow l
слова
t’s  the word par dota
теперь слово пар dota
what kind of person is in Lithuanian the words par
что за человек по-литовски слова пар
to give, well, not to or the right one to the laser
давать ну не на или правильная на лазер
, you immediately had the logic including the father’s garden and
у вас тут же логика включая саду отец и
give to give and so tapor dota and right there it
давать давать и так тапор dota и тут же
came guilty to rejoice
пришло там виноватый порадоваться
let’s succumb to the correct beep because before the
давайте поддаемся правильно бип ведь до
word
слова
sell  according to dota ca sold put a
продавать по dota ца продала поставьте
plus sign who are the types of reptiles and minus who has not
плюсик кто виды гадов а минус кто не
seen and
видал и
continue our group with us to the truth to the
продолжим нашу группу нас правде до
septic tank and when the website is
септика а когда сайте кого
correct so we look like
правильно итак смотрим вот
this in the
так
word accessible and
далее словом доступное и
who we are
кем мы
sharp and
остро и
rhythm and from the right states of noisy
ритма и от правильном ли штаты шумных
places
мест
still means the word  NATO hammer
еще означает слово натовской молот
then get out of your
то
mind
вылазь думки
and they see a good competition, I think
да и конкурса хороший видят я я считаю
that during the keiko team and if you
что во время кейко тим и если у тебя
have it, you need to donate not just something there
есть надо донатить не просто что-то там
but you have to wear something smart,
потреблять а надо носить что-то умное
so now we'll see how much the
так и вот сейчас мы посмотрим насколько
Lithuanian language is so similar to Russian, but
литовский язык так похоже на русский но
Ukraine is Ukrainian, that is, the common roots of
украина украинский то есть общие корни о
two ancient words, like if, for example,
двух древних слов как если например
let's get up who's kind, but
давайте поднимемся кто вида да
you are someone and in Russian  so
ты кто-то и по-русски так
put a plus sign, you guessed it,
поставьте плюсик то ведь гадал
yes, that is, 3 c, let's listen to the
да то есть 3 c она давайте прослушаем
measurement,
мерку
so we continue the distance, read vodka, then
так продолжаем даль почитай водки-то
long jets not a word out of wants already
длинные струи ни слова вон из хочет уже
rich moloch, come on, the first m sandal
богатых молох давай первых м сандаль
deliveries bit 0 to 10 for discounts, you are
поставки бит 0 до 10 на скидки вам
kidding toy che continue and
прикалываться игрушка че продолжают и
still  with a smaller pier and on the feet,
таки с меньшими молом и на ступни разы
put it from 0 to 10 times how
поставьте от 0 до 10 насколько вам
interesting this game is to you, but the treatment is
интересна такая игра но лечение
interesting pin 10 cool warmth of the soul
интересно pin 10 прикольно тепло души
class and we are on how we will try in the
класс и мы на при как будем пробовать в
region for hakim and
крае на хаким и просвечиваем наш стрим
we can see through our stream so in the stacker we are but for once the soul
так в stacker мы а вот за раз души
tsekalo and the words will
цекало и слова
give in ctos perhaps his growth is an abyss you are
подамся ctos возможно его рост бездна ты
so yes
так да
here almost to write what the
на почти до напишите что означает
words turgut mean in Lithuanian
по-литовски слова тургут
to your
на вашу думку
thought evgenia reddit foam as cool
евгении reddit пена качестве же классно
mike
майк
as usual  the word tour bus
как обычное слово tour bus
you are already difficult horses and the word
вы вы уже трудными лошадей и слова
ends the rope so that the verbs in
заканчивает канате так то что глаголы в
Lithuanian ends with 3 since
литовском заканчивается на 3 так как у
we have to do robots I have two types of rda
нас делать робыты я там два типа rda
they take the tour bus this is no longer a verb
they take the tour bus это уже не глагол
blizzard scenes Lydia words
пургу сцен лидии слова
she keeps saying
она-то твердит
it’s sacred to trade them to be traded by
свято торгово ты их быть торговать
Ivan ended in and so the diy words
иваном заканчивалась на и так diy слова
for the elements have already eclipsed so verse 3 it
на стихия уже затмив так стих 3 он и
ends with ti means a blizzard of the scene
заканчивается на ти значит пургу сцены
at the auction from the scarlet you correctly and immediately
на торгу от алая вы правильно и сразу
trifle tied chairs and so it
мелочиться повязана стульев и так то так
will turn on for so long and
давно включит и и
tour bus c
tour bus c
base
база
tap the tour densely bazaar places to
tap the tour густо базар места до
trade act jump top gear
торгуют актом прыжок top gear
top gear nectar sometimes
top gear нектар иногда
rich then right name interfere
богатых то правильно зовут мешаться
tied with trade and give dangerously there
повязана с торговлю и дать опасно там
tight you smile diy words note
туго ты улыбаешься diy слова ноте
ends and masturbate batchchat and die in
заканчивается и дрочи батчат и погибну в
slavic new ones there on whose court are you to
славянских новых там на чьей ты суд
know  ok doctors I read it means we are
узнать ok врачи я читал значит нас
kittytsy true ranks true there I am already a
китыци правда чины правда там уж я на я
linguist still tov skooma respected in the world
лингвист еще тов скума уважают на еблище
eats gaming move contagious bleach similar
ест игровых move заразный bleach схожую
will give it is hidden in the eu european n  I don’t know the
даст он скрыт у ес европейский не знаю
hotel is true on a lot from live and
гостиница правда на множество от живут и
dive far into ours and two words
погружаемся дальнем в нашей и два слова
ticked for you and
тикали для вас и
soldered for us the words
запайки за нас слова
dna
днк
still on your thought meaning the words of
еще на вашу думку означая слова генов
chikin’s genes you don’t know on the count of
чикина не знаете на кол оф
so
так
sea spa along the path elbows and
sea spa по тропе локти и
c words yes
c слова да
well here  vein in Lithuanian prays del and
ну вот вена на литовский молится del и
stop today the word
останина сегодня слово
will be with dea with a critical sign and such until
буду с dea критичными знаком и такими до
c again
c снова
I will not read out
я не буду зачитывать
because for clearly give a drink so I
потому что за четко дать питко так я не
will not read out this word try to
буду зачитывать это слово попробуйте по
guess its sound from the written and
написанному угадать его звучание и
understand that
понять что
she
она
lr loretta look profitable  it's taxation 4
lr лоретта взгляд выгодно это taxation 4
loretta is dying you don't play this
вымирает лоретта вы не играете в этой
game because you're from lithuania you know
игры потому что вы из литвы вы знаете
so
так
let me tell you how it reads
давайте я подскажу яко читает
put on airs and towers
важничать и башни
c&amp;c words meaning
c&amp;c слова означая
churches
церкви
put a plus sign puts bastards a lot here is the
поставьте плюсик ставит гадов куча вот
process of the word i read to the point who else to the
процесс слова я читал до сути кого еще к
word more had to drive  slavic
слову больше пришлось диск славянских
move there is still a god to lithuanian girls and
move там еще бог на литовский девочек и
get carried away once overgrown
увлекусь раза зарос
changed
изменен
to the side tops bunting will do and div the
в бок tops комола будет делать и div
words bozhnitsa frying kozhnitsa so it came
слова божнице жарки божнице так пришло
ukrainian  top from Russian 7 mare on the
украинскую топ с русскую 7 кобыла на
territory of ukraine on the territory of russia
территории украины на территории руси
because we were for yours, we didn’t
потому что мы были за твои вот не
keep the word
держали то слово
god benefit from it, yes, it turns out, but
бог выгода от его нужно да получается но
mundos and evgeny of the word devi you have it
mundos и евгений слова деви вас это у
in the plural you get the
вас в множественном числе получается
ending ac or it’s
окончании ac или
interesting the
интересно
beginning of
начало
our son  butt and there I already knew
нашей сына приклада и там уже знала
no literally in
никаких буквально
short, I mowed on a pair where this one from the
короче я косил на паре куда этот от
Tatars
татар
avoda Ismail Khan you write and the word God was
авода исмаил хан пишешь а слово бог был
borrowed from the Romano-Germanic
позаимствован до из романо-германской
sound environment until I understood everything, too,
звуковой среды до все понял тоже
with trying his corpse,
с пробовать его трупом испробовать
just trying to fix clusters in the year, then
просто числились кластера чиня в году то
try to be cool  yes
старайся прикольно да
[music]
[музыка]
well, I think that I was honored to give agro
хорошо я думаю что сподобилась дать агро
this is de affordable once we have a buda we
это де доступный раз у нас буда нас
will accept the outskirts so I will
примешь окраина так я к мы будем каждого
think of every stream Yakutsk rubber Akado
стрима загадывать якутск резиной акадо
help and Ukraine we will remember on every
помогай и украины мы будем на каждом
stream some country
стриме вспоминать какую-то страну
that helps Ukraine that eats
которая помогает украине которая ест
friendly kukri and we remembered
дружественной кукри и мы вспоминали
georgia now lithuania i won’t say who
грузию теперь литву не буду говорить кто
was remembering what country on
какую страну был вспоминать во вторник
tuesday but i  I will try to pick up some
так но я буду стараться подбирать про
interesting facts about this amount, and I
эту сумму кит интересные факты и вот мне
liked this game with some
понравилась вот эта игра с какими-то
words from the language of this country, so we
словами из языка этой страны так будем
would have pipes at home
бы дома
, so eye-catching this skin is Lithuanian, I
трубы так на глаз эту кожу литовские я
don’t know if they are people who are from Lithuania do you have an
не знаю она люди кто из литвы у вас есть
accent in the language
ударение в языке
andrey glazkova the next episode about
андрей глазкова следущий выпуск про
azerbaijan i won't be making the next
азербайджан я не буду пилить следующий
episode anyway, so you need
выпуск бы все-таки так так надо
to read the words one in british
прочитать слова один в британских
each each for each stream some
каждый каждую на каждый стрим какое-то
state will be new and will be
государство будет новый и будет
unknown to you before the start of the stream yes
неизвестная для вас до начала стрима да
there are
есть в литве
victor asmolov errors in lithuania  in the great external
виктор асмолов ошибок в великом внешним
top 100, the prayer did not have a written language,
топ-100 молитва не имела письменности
so many words in meaning were
поэтому много слов по смыслу были
written in your letters, by the way, I’m not a
записаны вашими буквами ну кстати я не
historian, but in my opinion I read that the Grand
историк но по-моему я читал что великой
Duchess of Lithuania and writing
княжны литовском и письменность
were carried out on a pen, maybe with in
проводились на ручке может с на
Ukrainian, to whom
украинском языке на кого
part q Slovak pliz  everything will be like this and the
часть q словацкую плиз все будет так и
ice is too cold for the stream, I myself
льду же дуже дякую за стрим мне самому
became tick on this I would you decide so
стало тиковых на это я вы решили бы вот
I respect that here I am the smoke of the elevator we have a
я уважаю что вот я дым лифта у нас дуже
lot of people there  I strive for streams and there it
багато людей там стремлюсь стримы и там
just teases from the Russians of the USA I love
просто дразнит из россиян сша я обожаю
prices for completely designers and peacocks of
цены совсем конструкторам и павлиний
Poland
польши
like new denunciations with the Russians you date their
вроде новые с россиянам доносы ты дат их
Russians cinema table mind is not a thought
россияне кино таблица разум не думки так
and the brightness of the rich
и яркость богачу
in I watched a lot of streamers so different
в я смотрел много стримеров так разных
not then they drive something fooling around
не потом там что-то дурачатся гонят
Russians, I think that during the
русских я считаю что надо во время
stream we use a colossal time
стрима мы используем колоссальной время
and a colossal audience, we also need to
и колоссальную аудиторию надо до людей
convey some thoughts to people from Russia,
из россии тоже доносить какие-то мысли
thoughts correctly and they will remain involved,
мысли правильно и участие они останутся
and we also need to somehow
и так же надо как-то
enrich ourselves, so I think that
обогащать себя так вот я думаю что мы
today we are with ourselves  rich to like new
сегодня себя с богаты лайкать новую
information who was bullying for rent is it possible
информацию кто задирался напрокат можно
to rent your Lithuanian pier and so we
ли твои литовской мол и так мы
enriched information about lithuania someone
обогатились информация про литву кто-то
became interested someone reads more
заинтересовался кто-то почитает больше
so you will be surprised by the denunciation of the 17th century lithuania
так вот вы удивитесь донос 17 века литва
almost 15 times reduced its
чуть ли не в 15 раз уменьшило свои
size so that is it was  a huge
размеры так то есть это было огромное
state that included the territory of
государство которая включала территорию
modern Belarus, part of
современной там еще и белоруссии части
Ukraine, part of Poland, so it
украины части польши так это огромное
was a very developed state  by the way,
было очень развитое государство я кстати
when I was in Vilnius, it’s like I’m
когда был вильнюсе так я как бы совсем
completely different Lithuania from the boarding school and Lithuania,
по другому литва из интерната и литва
when you want to appear there, you
когда ты хочешь там появились у ты
see a really cool European city
видишь реально крутой европейский город
with huge stories, the history that the
с огромной историй история которые
Russian Empire hides us, she
российская империя нас скрывает она
wanted to trample on our Belarus, so
хотела затоптать наш белоруссия так
Belarus, well, also part of the great
белоруссия ну тоже частью великого
the principality of Lithuania, yes, but for some reason, the
княжества литовского да но почему-то
history of Belarus brings up the history of Belarus, there was the
историю беларуси доводит вот было был
USSR there was still the Russian empire, the
ссср был там еще российской империи
calculations of the Belarusians used to have no
подсчётам у белорусов раньше было не
story numbers, alas, our
рассказ нoмep увы не рухаты наши
informative front and in the freedom of good
информативный фронт и в свободы добр
nothing is easy
ничего не бывает легко старшую разу
places 2 our entire stream write who from
места 2 вся наш стрим напишите кто из
which city watched our stream I will be in
какого города смотрел наш стрим я буду в
this one and enjoy the discounts at the court andrey
этой и радоваться скидки на суде андрей
what do you think it’s Dagestan here is
что думаете это же дагестане вот
tajikistan
таджикистан
in principle a state with a typical
в принципе государства с типичной
Asian model of governance so that is,
азиатской модели управления так то есть
there are some democratic reforms and I
там какие-то демократических реформ и не
don’t think  what are expected for the
думаю что ожидаются на
coming years,
ближайшие годы
for example, if we look at Turkey, so the Turks
например если смотрим турцию так турки
are also good  Turkmens are kindred
они тоже хоть и туркмены родственные
peoples, they
народы они
came to this price. Turks, they are in the process of
пришли эту цену турки они в процессе
developing their own as a state, they
развития своего как государство они
have become very civilized, so that is,
очень цивилизованными стали так то есть
no one will say
никто не скажет
Turkey is somehow a backward country,
турция там как-то отсталая страна по
let’s say with our own
скажем своим
eyes, they have
взглядом то у них есть это реакционные
certain reactionary forces, but that’s all they are
определенные силы но такого всего они
the whole new European civilization is already integrating,
уже интегрируется все новую европейскую
so it’s called the greatest
так это называется наибольшее rich
richness of the kalitva,
калитвы
I don’t know, honestly,
не знаю не знаю честно
Chechnya, a couple of Ukraine, Lenin came up with a
чечне паре украина придумал ленин
Dwight and Bakhman,
дуайтом и бахман силами на
but didn’t trample it, but is
но не затоптала да а
it a fall of leaves to fall paws crisis
листопад ли впадать лап кризис
sim who everyone who was from Lithuania with us on the
сим кто всем кто был из литвы с нами на
stream is huge  like so despite
стриме вам огромнейшее лайк так несмотря
the fact that it is
на то что вам украинский язык
not very easy for
не совсем легко возможно воспринимать
you to perceive the Ukrainian language as but you perceive it cool and we
как но вы воспринимать это круто и мы
also try to enrich our knowledge about the
стараемся тоже обогащать свое знание о
peoples friendly to us glory to ukraine
дружественных нам народов слава украине
and freedom of peoples
и свободу народов
[music]
[музыка]
remind me I will
пришел ваш донат я 6 напомнить я ее
voice it in I will voice it just in case I
озвучу в я на всяк случай озвучу бы я
remind you I don’t remember or
напоминаю не помню или
so that’s all ev  ents my heart didn’t
так что все events у меня сердце не
worry that I didn’t voice you waiting for
переживала что я не озвучил вас жду на
so I didn’t remember he jumped out I won’t say
так я не помнили он выскочил не скажу
anything terrible twice we’ll show if
ничего страшного два раза покажем если
that sec
что сек
[music]
[музыка]